

Madhusudan Panda

UX/Motion Graphic Designer

SKILLS

Creativity
Typography
Technology
Communication

ABOUT ME

Creative UX designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. **2** years of experience developing designs for mobile apps, websites, Graphic video, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs.

SOFTWARE

Management

Photoshop

Illustrator
Premiere
After effects
Adobe XD

EDUCATION

2010-2012 CHSE,ODISHA
Council of higher secondary education in (Arts)

2012-2015 SCTE & VT,ODISHA
Diploma in (Mechanical Engineering).

2015-2018 BPUT,ODISHA
Bachelor of Technology in (Mechanical Engineering).

LANGUAGES

English
Hindi
Oriya

EXPERIENCE

2018-2019 NSDC

National Skill Development

Corporation (Skill India) as a Assessor.

2019-present Genii IT Services Pvt. Ltd.

Working as a UX/MotionGraphic/Graphic
Designer in Tradin project.

CONTACT



madhusudan.panda1@gmail.com



9861616961



Hyderabad, Telangana



HOBBIES





https://grafo-designer.github.io/grafo/



https://www.linkedin.com/in/madhusudan-panda-aa833519b/